# Thomas Crowe Greenville, SC

wtcrowe4@outlook.com | 864-630-3512 | Thomas Crowe | LinkedIn

GitHub: <a href="https://github.com/wtcrowe4">https://github.com/wtcrowe4</a> | Website: <a href="https://thomascrowe.netlify.app">https://thomascrowe.netlify.app</a>

#### **PROFESSIONAL SUMMARY**

Programming enthusiast who excels at learning new languages and technologies. Agile problem solver with experience building efficient full-stack applications utilizing multiple data management solutions. Motivated and committed professional who will go above and beyond to ensure tasks and projects are completed correctly in a timely manner. A team player with the ability to create relationships built on trust and support with co-workers and clients alike.

#### **EDUCATION**

N.C. State University Raleigh, NC

Software Development Certificate Program 2022

Courses: HTML, CSS, JavaScript, UIUX, Express, React, PostgreSQL, SQL, Python, Flask, Cybersecurity, SCSS, Typescript, AWS

<u>Clemson University</u> Clemson, SC

125 Credit Hours in Computer Science and Computer Engineering 2009-2012

#### **SKILLS PROFILE**

 $\textbf{Development Technologies:} \ \textbf{HTML}, \textbf{CSS}, \textbf{SCSS}, \textbf{JavaScript}, \textbf{Typescript}, \textbf{ThreeJS}, \textbf{Node}, \textbf{Express}, \textbf{Python}, \textbf{Flask}, \textbf{Django}, \textbf{C\#}, .\textbf{NET}, \textbf{CSS}, \textbf{CS$ 

MAUI, Redux, React, Angular, Svelte, Tailwind, Bootstrap, Git, GitHub

Databases: MongoDB, PostgreSQL, SQL

Security: Identity and Access Management, Multi-factor Authentication, Google Authentication, Data Encryption

**Deployment Tools:** Heroku, AWS, Netlify, Azure

### **PROJECT EXPERIENCE**

#### **Grocery-List | N.C. State**

**6**/2022

• A creative MERN stack application for making personal grocery lists, enhanced by a recipe API, utilizing user registration and login with bcrypt and JWT, Nodemailer.

#### **Sports Book | Independent Project**

8/2022

A lightweight React application for real-time sports scores and odds utilizing an API to keep data up to date.

## **Crowe Realty | Independent Project**

11/2022

A responsive full-stack application designed for listing residential properties using Angular, C#, and SQL.

#### **Discord Clone | N.C. State**

A full-stack mobile friendly application intended to resemble Discord, using Django and SQL.

# **MAUI Finance | Independent Project**

3/2023-Present

A cross platform .NET MAUI mobile application to keep up with stock data using a financial API.

#### **MAUI Golf | Independent Project**

7/2023-Present

• A .NET MAUI mobile application with authentication, APIs, and SQL database to keep track of golfer's stats and handicap.

#### PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCE

### Arnold's Famous Hamburgers: Anderson/Pickens County, SC

8/2016-Present

Manager

- Responsible for day-to-day operations, and ensuring every customer has a good experience.
- Exceptional customer service and conflict resolution skills with the ability to create great relationships.
- Using inventiveness to implement new ways to increase profit and sales with rising food costs post-pandemic.
- Built strong problem-solving and adaptive skills from managing multiple locations through the COVID pandemic.
- Utilizing interpersonal skills daily in a fast paced, high-pressure environment.
- Occasional debugging and set-up improvements for our point of sales Clover machines and software.

### **Outback Steakhouse: Easley, SC**

5/2011-3/2016

## Bartender

- Used planning and organization skills to manage stock of alcohol.
- Required to thrive in demanding and stressful situations while keeping a good attitude.
- Networked with bar guests while ensuring great service and making sure other diners got drinks quickly.
- Created strong relationships which developed many regular customers.
- Cultivated the ability to find things in common with anyone who dined with us.